You're Invited to a Party... We'll Play the Deadliest
Game of All... Hunting 26 Men and 1 Woman!
The Hunting Party is a western film directed by Don Medford.
A ruthless rancher, and his gang, use extremely long range
rifles to kill the men who kidnapped his wife.
Frank Calder, played by Oliver Reed.
Melissa Ruger, played by Candice Bergen.
Brandt Ruger, played by Gene Hackman.
Matthew Gunn, played by Simon Oakland.
Doc Harrison, played by Mitchell Ryan.
Hog Warren, played by L.Q. Jones.
The Hunting Party is a 1971 American-British western film, directed by Don Medford for Levy-Gardner-Laven
and starring Oliver Reed, Gene Hackman, Candice Bergen, Simon Oakland and Ronald Howard.
The film was shot at studios in Madrid and on location around
Spain, including the Tabernas Desert in Andalusia.
The film's sets were designed by the art director Enrique Alarcón.
The film explores themes of infidelity, wife, texas, ranch, rifle.